<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Fiction</string>

    <string name="topics">Topics</string>

    <string name="culture_and_society">Culture &amp; Society</string>
    <string name="mind_and_philosophy">Mind &amp; Philosophy</string>
    <string name="personal_growth">Personal growth</string>

    <string name="favorites_list">Favorites List</string>

    <string name="about_this_book">About this book</string>
    <string name="what_will_you_learn_from_this_book">What will you learn from this book?</string>

    <string name="name_1">The good guy</string>
    <string name="author_1">Mark Mcallister</string>
    <string name="book_description_1">"The Good Guy" by Mark McAlister is a story about an ordinary person who finds himself
        caught in a whirlwind of criminal events. As his world crumbles, he is forced to confront the dark sides of society and his own morality.
        He must seek answers to complex questions about good and evil, justice and revenge.
        His journey is not only a struggle against external forces, but also an internal transformation,
        where he discovers new facets of his personality and rethinks his place in the world.
    </string>

    <string name="name_2">Norse Mythology</string>
    <string name="author_2">Neil Gaiman</string>
    <string name="book_description_2">The great Norse myths, which have inspired so much of modern fiction,
        are dazzlingly retold by Neil Gaiman. Tales of dwarfs and frost giants, of treasure and magic, and of Asgard,
        home to the gods: Odin the all-father, highest and oldest of the Aesir; his mighty son Thor,
        whose hammer Mjollnir makes the mountain giants tremble; Loki, wily and handsome, reliably unreliable in his lusts;
        and Freya, more beautiful than the sun or the moon, who spurns those who seek to control her.
    </string>

    <string name="name_3">Futurama</string>
    <string name="author_3">Michael Douglas</string>
    <string name="book_description_3">"Futurama: Upgrade Your Brain Without Breaking Your Mind" is a captivating science
        fiction adventure that transports readers into a wondrous world of the future. In this world, where technology has
        reached incredible heights and interplanetary travel has become commonplace, the protagonist embarks on a quest for
        a mysterious technology capable of enhancing the human mind. But along the way, he encounters dangerous trials,
        incredible creatures, and philosophical questions about the nature of consciousness and the limits of human potential.
        Will he be able to unravel the secret of brain upgrades without losing himself?
    </string>

    <string name="name_4">Explore Your Creativity</string>
    <string name="author_4">Colby Sharp</string>
    <string name="book_description_4">"Unlock Your Creative Mind to Positivity: A Habit That Will Transform Your Life"
        is an inspiring and practical guide to unlocking your creative potential and harnessing it for positive change.
        Colby Sharp, a renowned author and educator, shares simple yet powerful techniques to cultivate creative thinking,
        overcome creative blocks, and leverage creativity for emotional well-being. The book explores the profound connection
        between creativity and positive mindset, demonstrating how creative expression can alleviate stress, boost self-esteem,
        and foster greater life satisfaction.
    </string>
</resources>